Now if I play "extract,"
it would be cheating.
(Leonard:)- Sorry.
- Although, I could play...
(Sheldon:)...the completely unrelated
and better word "extract."
(Sheldon:)Ethical conundrum avoided.
(Sheldon:)Thanks, brain.
(Penny:)Spaghetti okay?
(Leonard:)It's crunchy.
(Leonard:)Just the way I like it.
(Penny:)Yeah, I don't think
the water was really boiling.
- It's great, I love it.
- Ha, ha.
(Penny:)Okay, listen, there's something
I need to tell you.
(Penny:)I've been thinking about
going back to school for a while now.
(Penny:)So a couple months ago, I started taking
a history class at the community college.
(Leonard:)Oh. That's great. Great, great, great.
(Leonard:)- Why wait so long to tell me?
- I just...
(Penny:)I don't want you to make
a big deal out of it.
Why do you think that?
I get it, you're taking one class.
(Leonard:)It's nice. Maybe if it goes well,
you take another, you enroll full time.
(Leonard:)Ooh. Be sure to keep an eye on which
credits transfer to a four-year college.